Guide to the Athletics and Recreation Department records, 1890-2009 RG0054
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Programs, guides, posters, profiles, and shirt, 1995-1996; RG0054 Series 9; 1 Linear foot
  This series consists of sports programs, all-sports media guides, posters, player profiles, and a felt basketball shirt. The material ranges in date from 1995-96.
  Formerly ACC#544, formerly RG6.4
  - Women's Basketball Game Schedule and Poster, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Men's Basketball Game Schedule and Poster, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Basketball Promotional Jersey "Colonials", undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Blue
  - Fall Sports Game Schedules, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Four copies
  - Women's Basketball Schedule, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Two copies
  - Men's Basketball Schedule, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - George Washington's All American Volleyball: "Sveltana Vtyurina" Student Profile, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - George Washington's All American Volleyball: "Tajma Abraham" Student Profile, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - George Washington's All American Volleyball: "Alexander Koul" Student Profile, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - George Washington's All American Volleyball: "Kwame Evans" Student Profile, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - GW Baseball Media Guide, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - GW Crew Media Guide, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - GW Cross Country Media Guide, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - GW Men's Soccer Media Guide, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - GW Women's Soccer Media Guide, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - GW Water Polo Media Guide, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - GW Volleyball Media Guide, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - GW Women's Basketball Media Guide, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - GW Men's Basketball Media Guide, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - GW Men's & Women's Basketball Media Guide: "Colonials Courtside", 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Football team photographs, 1930-1960; RG0054 Series 10; 3 Linear feet (Box 1, Box 2)
  This series consists of football team photographs. The materials range in date from 1930-60.
  Formerly ACC#591, formerly RG6.4
  This series is unprocessed, please ask staff for assistance
- Women's rifle club collection, 1947-1959; RG0054 Series 11; 1 Linear foot (Box 1, Box 2)
  This series consists of materials dealing with budget, equipment, National Rifle Association, inventory, and also contains manuals, score sheets, match results, photographs and a scrapbook from the women's rifle team. The materials range in date from 1947-59.
  Formerly ACC#264
  - GWU Athletic Association, 1939-1943 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Includes constitution
  - Financial records, 1930-1959 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Budget, 1929-1960 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Equipment, 1936-1947 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - National Rifle Association certificates, 1942-1950 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - National Rifle Association correspondence, 1925-1956 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Ammunition orders, 1950-1952 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Inventories, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Manuals, 1934-1964 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Matches and scores, 1928-1954 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Score books, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Intramural matches, A-B, 1927-1952 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Intramural matches, C, 1932-1953 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Intramural matches, D-F, 1927-1952 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Intramural matches, G, 1934-1953 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Intramural matches, H-J, 1928-1953 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Intramural matches, K-L, 1927-1954 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Intramural matches, M, 1926-1954 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Intramural matches, N-P, 1927-1954 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Intramural matches, Q-R, 1932-1953 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Intramural matches, S-Z, 1928-1953 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Match results, 1952-1953 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Scrapbook copies, 1921-1963 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Photographs, 1950 ca. (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Trophies, 1943-1994; RG0054 Series 12; 7.5 Linear feet
  This series consists of 9 trophies. The materials range in date from 1943-1994.
  Formerly ACC#620, formerly RG6.4. Formerly ACC#206, formerly RG 6.4.2
  - Southern Conference Basketball Champions, 1943 (Object 1)
  - Southern Conference Baseball Champions, 1956 (Object 2)
  - Southern Conference Baseball Champions, 1959 (Object 3)
  - S. L. Sommer Trophy GWU Letterman's Club Golf Champion, 1957-1973 (Object 4)
    1957 - H.M. Kiesel, 1958 - H.M. Kiesel, 1959 - Joe Gallagher, 1960 - Pete Cabukas; R.H. Fenlon, 1961 - H.M. Kiesel, 1962 - Tad Linder, 1963 - Ellis Hall, 1964 - Mike Millan, 1965 - Tad Linder, 1966 - Tad Linder, 1966 - Mike Millan, 1967 - Bob Fores, 1967 - Harvey Shipman, 1967 - Bill Amos, 1968 - Andy Davis, 1971 - Larry Spellman, 1973 - Bernie Good
  - The Letterman's Trophy, 1963-1970 (Object 5)
    Awarded Annually to the City Intercollegiate Champion by the GWU Alumni Letterman's Club; Georgetown University 1963-1964; Maryland University 1964-1965, Maryland University 1969-70
  - Women's Gymnastics GWU Invitational - Second Team, 1984 (Object 6)
  - Women's Volleyball Colonial Invitational 2nd place, 1984 (Object 7)
  - Women's Varsity Crawford Bay Crew Classic - Mayor's Cup, 1994 (Object 8)
  - George Washington University Volleyball Invitational 1st place, 1985 (Object 9)
- Program and ticket, 1953; RG0054 Series 13; 0.5 Linear foot (Box 1)
  This series consists of a program and ticket for GW vs. West Virginia football game on October 16, 1953.
  Formerly ACC#688, formerly RG6.4
  - Program and ticket for GW vs. West Virginia, 10/16/1953 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Jump rope, 1999; RG0054 Series 14; 1 Linear foot (Box 1)
  This series consists of one jump rope from dedication of Wellness Center. The material dates from 1999.
  Formerly ACC#736, formerly RG6.4
- Banners, ca.1995; RG0054 Series 16; 1 Linear foot (Box 1)
  This series consists of three banners: one Atlantic 10 conference banner and two George Washington women's basketball.
  Formerly ACC#815, formerly RG6.4
- Cheerleader uniforms, 1993-1998; RG0054 Series 17; 1 Linear foot (Box 1)
  This series consists of four cheerleader uniforms. The material range in date from 1993-98.
  Formerly ACC#821, RG6.4
  - Blue Male Uniform - top and pants, 1995-1998 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Blue Female Uniform - top and skirt, 1995-1998 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Gold Male Uniform - top and pants, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Gold Female Uniform - top and skirt, 1993-1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Departmental files, 1907-2005; RG0054 Series 18; 2 Linear feet
  This series contains flyers, brochures, programs, a calendar, memorandums, posters, letterhead, guidelines, guides, stickers, colonials patchs, invitations, news releases, photographs, reports, schedules, rules, handbooks, newsletters, bumper stickers, biographic information, tickets, agreements, press pass, and conference proceeding. They range in date from 1907 to 2005. They concern events and athletics within the Smith Center; dedication of the Smith Center; fundraising; visiting team information; highlights and facts of different sports; publications; ticket information; tournaments; wellness programs; sports medicine; lectures; Colonial Club; golf, tennis, and water polo prospectuses; awards; cheerleading cheers; boosters; women's and men's hall of fame; history; intramural and extramural sports; touch football rules; National collegiate Athletic Association (NCAA); mascot; inercollegiate athletics; Eastern Conference Basketball League (ECBL); coaches and athletic directors; player statistic; Cherry Blossom Invitational Crew Classic; scouting reports; Women's Basketball Press; All-American canidates; and Womean's Recreation Association (WRA).
  Formerly vertical files. Staff unable to locate Box 1.
  - Colonnade Gallery Exhibit, "GW Basketball: Past, Present, and Future", 1966-1993 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Includes men's basketball photographs
  - Colonnade Gallery Exhibit, "GW Basketball: Past, Present, and Future", 1993 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Colonnade Gallery Exhibit, "GW Basketball: Past, Present, and Future", 1979-1982 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Includes photographs
  - Colonnade Gallery Exhibit, "GW Basketball: Past, Present, and Future", 1993 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Includes photographs, 1960s-1980s
  - Promotional material, 1975-1990 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Letterman's sweaters, 1933-1968; RG0054 Series 19; 1 Linear foot (Flat box 1)
  This series consists of two letterman's sweaters: blue sweater with George Washington University patch (donated by William Noonan, class of 1937) and blue sweater with 1968 football patch (donated by Johnny Fenlon, class of 1933.)
  Formerly ACC#878, formerly RG6.4
  - Noonan's Football Letterman Sweater, 1933 ca. (Flat box 1, Folder 1)
  - Johny Fenlon's Football Letterman Sweater, 1968 ca. (Flat box 1, Folder 2)
  - Football Letterman Sweater, ca. 1930 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Football Letterman Sweater, ca. 1930 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - J.R. Brown Football Letterman Sweater, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - J.R. Brown photograph and football program, 1930 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Basketball ephemera, 1990-2005; RG0054 Series 20; 1.5 Linear feet (Box 1)
  This series consists of basketball pennants, pom-poms, towels, patches, megaphones, commemorative cups and tins. This material ranges in date from 1990-2005.
  Formerly ACC#886, formerly RG6.4
  - Mini pom-pons, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    8 items
  - Colonials Buttons, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    2 items
  - GW Colonials headband, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - 1993 Commencement pins, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - GW lettermen's patches, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - GWU patches, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Colonials Basketball bumper stickers, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - GW Colonials basketball tea towels, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
    7 items
  - GW Colonials basketball hand towels, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Colonials megaphones, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
    5 items
  - GW pennants, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Colonials pennants, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - GW Colonials foam hatchets, undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - GW Colonials We're #1 foam hands, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Windshield ice scraper GW Basketball, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - GWU Colonials key chain, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Plastic cup, Women's Basketball 2002 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Commemorative popcorn tin, Men's Basketball, 2005 Atlantic-10 Champions, NCAA Tournament, Nashville TN (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Football ponchos, 1960; RG0054 Series 21; 1 Linear foot (Flat box 1)
  This series consists of two ponchos from football team from 1960.
  Formerly ACC#914, formerly RG6.4
- Colonials Sports News, 1968-2004; RG0054 Series 22; 3.0 Linear feet (Box 4, Box 1, Box 2, Box 3)
  This series consists of Colonial Sports News materials: news, press releases, and team statistics from all sports from the Director of Sports Information.
  The material range in date from 1968-92 and 1995-97
  Formerly ACC#921
  - Sports news, press releases and team statistics, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Sports news, press releases and team statistics, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Sports news, press releases and team statistics, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Sports news, press releases and team statistics, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Sports news, press releases and team statistics, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Sports news, press releases and team statistics, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Sports news, press releases and team statistics, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Sports news, press releases and team statistics, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Sports news, press releases and team statistics, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Sports news, press releases and team statistics, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Sports news, press releases and team statistics, 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Sports news, press releases and team statistics, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Sports news, press releases and team statistics, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Sports news, press releases and team statistics, 1981-1982 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Sports news, press releases and team statistics, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Sports news, press releases and team statistics, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Sports news, press releases and team statistics, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Sports news, press releases and team statistics, 1985-1986 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Sports news, press releases and team statistics, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Sports news, press releases and team statistics, 01/1988-06/1988 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Sports news, press releases and team statistics, 07/1988-10/1988 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Sports news, press releases and team statistics, 11/1988-12/1988 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Sports news, colonial weekly update, 01/1989-02/1989 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Sports news, colonial weekly update, 03/1989-04/1989 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Sports news, press releases and team statistics, 05/1989-06/1989 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Sports news, baseball recruitments, 07/1989-08/1989 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Sports news, colonial athletic weekly update, 09/1989 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Sports news, colonial athletic weekly update, 10/1989 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Sports news, colonial athletic weekly update, 11/1989 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Sports news, colonial athletic weekly update, 12/1989 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Sports news, colonial athletic weekly update, 01/1990 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Sports news, colonial athletic weekly update, 02/1990 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Sports news, colonial athletic weekly update, 03/1990 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Sports news, colonial athletic weekly update, 04/1990 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Sports news, colonial athletic weekly update, 05/1990 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Sports news, basketball, volleyball, soccer, coaches, swimming program, etc., 07/1990-08/1990 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Sports news, colonials athletics weekly update, women's tennis, men's soccer, volleyball etc., 09/1990 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Sports news, colonial athletic weekly update, 10/1990 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Sports news, colonial athletic weekly update, 11/1990 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Sports news, colonial athletic weekly update, 12/1990 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Sports news, colonial athletic weekly update, 01/1991 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Sports news, colonial athletic weekly update, 02/1991 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Sports news, colonial athletic weekly update, 03/1991-04/1991 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Sports news, colonial athletic weekly update, 05/1991-06/1991 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Sports news, colonial athletic weekly update, 09/1991 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Sports news, colonial athletic weekly update, 10/1991 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Sports news, colonial athletic weekly update, 11/1991 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Sports news, colonial athletic weekly update, basketball statistics, 12/1991 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Sports news, colonial athletic weekly update, 01/1992 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Sports news, colonial athletic weekly update, 02/1992 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Sports news, baseball statistics, colonial athletic weekly update, 03/1992 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Sports news, baseball statistics, colonial athletic weekly update, 04/1992 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Colonial sports information, 1995-1997 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Sports news, undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Sports news, colonial athletic weekly update, 05/1992 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Sports news, colonial athletic weekly update, 06/1992 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Sports news, colonial athletic weekly update, 09/1992 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 10/05/1992 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 10/12/1992 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 10/19/1992 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 10/26/1992 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 11/02/1992 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 11/09/1992 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 11/16/1992 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 11/23/1992 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 11/30/1992 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 12/07/1992 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 12/14/1992 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 12/28/1992 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 01/1993 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 02/1993 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 03/1993 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 04/1993 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 05/1993 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 06/1993 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 07/1993 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 08/1993 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 09/1993 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 10/1993 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 11/1993 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 12/1993 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 01/1994 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 02/1994 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 03/1994 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 04/1994 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 05/1994 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 06/1994 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 08/1994 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 09/1994 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 10/1994 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 11/1994 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 12/1994 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 01/1995 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 02/1995 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 03/1995 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 04/1995 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 05/1995 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 06/1995 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 08/1995 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 09/1995 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 10/1995 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 11/1995 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 12/1995 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 01/1996 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 02/1996 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 03/1996 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 04/1996 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 05/1996 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 06/1996 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 07/1996 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 08/1996 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 09/1996 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 10/1996 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 02/1997 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 03/1997 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 04/1997 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 05/1997 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 06/1997 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 08/1997 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 09/1997 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 10/1997 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 11/1997 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 12/1997 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 01/1998 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 02/1998 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 03/1998 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 04/1998 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 05/1998 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 06/1998 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 07/1998 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 08/1998 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 09/1998 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 10/1998 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 11/1998 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 12/1998 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 01/1999 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 02/1999 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 03/1999 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 04/1999 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 05/1999 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 06/1999 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 07/1999 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 08/1999 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 09/1999 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 10/1999 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 11/1999 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 12/1999 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 01/2000 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 02/2000 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 03/2000 (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 04/2000 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - Colonial sports press releases, 05/2000 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - GW Sports Communications press releases, 06/2000 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - GW Sports Communications press releases, 07/2000 (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - GW Sports Communications press releases, 08/2000 (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - GW Sports Communications press releases, 09/2000 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - GW Sports Communications press releases, 10/2000 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - GW Sports Communications press releases, 11/2000 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - GW Sports Communications press releases, 12/2000 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - GW Sports Communications press releases, 01/2001 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - GW Sports Communications press releases, 02/2001 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - GW Sports Communications press releases, 03/2001 (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - GW Sports Communications press releases, 04/2001 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - GW Sports Communications press releases, 05/2001 (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - GW Sports Communications press releases, 06/2001 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - GW Sports Communications press releases, 07/2001 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - GW Sports Communications press releases, 08/2001 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - GW Sports Communications press releases, 09/2001 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - GW Sports Communications press releases, 10/2001 (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - GW Sports Communications press releases, 11/2001 (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - GW Sports Communications press releases, 12/2001 (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - GW Sports Communications press releases, 01/2002 (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - GW Sports Communications press releases, 02/2002 (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - GW Sports Communications press releases, 03/2002 (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - GW Sports Communications press releases, 04/2002 (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - GW Sports Communications press releases, 05/2002 (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - GW Sports Communications press releases, 06/2002 (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - GW Sports Communications press releases, 07/2002 (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - GW Sports Communications press releases, 08/2002 (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - GW Sports Communications press releases, 09/2002 (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - GW Sports Communications press releases, 10/2002 (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - GW Sports Communications press releases, 11/2002 (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - GW Sports Communications press releases, 12/2002 (Box 4, Folder 126)
  - GW Sports Communications press releases, 01/2003 (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - GW Sports Communications press releases, 02/2003 (Box 4, Folder 128)